（走过的路）
上帝
God.
我是图妮·贝维尔
Toni Bevell.
记录者 伦敦分会的
Men of Letters, London Chapterhouse.
他们派我来抓你
They sent me to take you in.
- 把枪放下 - 站住
- Put the gun down. - Stop.
你和我都知道你是不会扣下扳机的
You and I both know you're not gonna pull the trigger.
你给了我我最需要的
You gave me what I needed most.
我想给予你同样的回报
I want to do the same for you.
妈妈
Mom?
（如今）
我
I, uh…
你是…
Are you…
真的吗
really…real?
我在哪
Where am I?
你是谁
Who the hell are you?
我是迪恩
I'm … I'm Dean.
温彻斯特 你儿子
Winchester. I'm your son.
不
No.
我的迪恩才四岁
My Dean is 4 years old.
你死的时候我是四岁
I was when you died.
萨姆 萨姆
Sammy. Sammy!
妈妈
Mom.
听我说
Listen to me.
你叫玛丽·桑德拉·坎贝尔
Your name … your name is Mary Sandra Campbell, okay?
你生于1954年12月5日
You were born December 5, 1954,
父母是萨穆埃尔和迪安娜·坎贝尔
to Samuel and Deanna Campbell.
你父亲为了工作四处漂泊
Your father, he bounced around a lot for, uh, work,
你也一直跟随他
and you bounced right along with him,
最后你在堪萨斯州劳伦斯落脚
and you ended up in Lawrence, Kansas.
你怎么知道的
How do you know all that?
爸爸告诉我的
Dad told me.
1972年3月23日
March 23, 1972,
你走出了一家电影院
you walked out of a movie theater …
刚看完《第五屠宰场》
"Slaughterhouse-Five."
你超喜欢
You loved it,
你撞上了一个大块头海军陆战队员
and you bumped into a big Marine.
你把他撞倒了
and you knocked him flat on his ass.
你觉得很不好意思 他却一笑而过
You were embarrassed, and he laughed it off,
说你请他喝杯咖啡就没事了
said you could make it up to him with a cup of coffee.
于是你们去了穆罗尼餐厅
So, you went to, uh, Mulroney's.
你们聊了起来
and you talked.
他很可爱
and he was cute.
他知道每首齐柏林飞船的歌
and he knew the words to every Zeppelin song,
所以他要你电话的时候
so when he asked you for your number,
你就给了他
you gave it to him,
虽然你知道你爸会气坏的
even though you knew your dad would be pissed.
那一晚 你遇见了
That was the night that … that you met …
约翰·温彻斯特
John Winchester.
1975年8月19日 你们结婚了
August 19, 1975, you were married…
在雷诺结的
in Reno.
你的点子
Your idea.
几年后 我就出生了
A few years later, I came along,
然后是萨姆
then Sammy.
然后我烧死了
And then I burned.
我离开多久了
How long have I been gone?
33年
33 years.
迪恩
Dean.
妈妈
Hi, Mom.
[邪恶力量 第12季第1集]
老天爷
Holy mother.
我在哪
Where am I?
地球上
Earth?
不
No.
我离堪萨斯州的黎巴嫩有多远
How far am I from Lebanon, Kansas?
三个小时吧
Th-three hours, maybe.
等等 你是谁…你是什么
Wait, wait, wait, wait. Who … What are you, man?
他怎么死的
How did he die?
他为了我牺牲了
He gave himself up for me.
约翰就是这样的人
That sounds like John.
他成了猎人
And he was a Hunter?
他把你和萨姆也培养成了
And he raised you and Sam to…
是的
Yeah, he did.
你说我们以前见过
And you said we've met before,
你时空旅行的时候
when you traveled through time.
两次呢
Twice.
你的记忆被抹去了 所以
Your memory got wiped, so…
我做鬼的时候还见过你
And I saw you when I was a ghost…
这我也不记得了
which I don't remember, either.
上帝的妹妹把我复活了
And God's…sister brought me back to life?
差不多
Pretty much.
是挺难接受
It's a lot.
这我知道
And I know it's a lot.
我会解释一切的
And I'll explain everything. I will.
但现在 我们得走了
But right now, let's get out of here.
我带你回家吧
Let's get you home.
走吧 妈妈
Come on, Mom.
格雷戈里·马里恩医生吗
Dr. Gregory Marion?
我需要你帮忙
I need your help.
这才早上六点
It's … It's 6:00 a.m.
情况紧急
It's an emergency.
女士 等等
Lady, hold up.
你家后屋有座诊所
You have a clinic at the back of your house.
应该物品齐全吧
I trust it's fully stocked.
女士 真的
Lady. Lady, seriously.
除非你的狗狗被车撞了还是什么的
Unless your uh … your puggle got hit by a car or something,
不急这一时
it can wait.
真的很急
It really can't.
他腿部中了枪
He was shot in the leg.
一枪 .38子弹
A single, .38-caliber bullet.
把子弹挖出来 缝好伤口
I need the round dug out, the wound sutured,
再给我点麻醉带走
and some anesthesia to go.
不行
No.
别想
No way.
我是兽医
I'm a veterinarian.
动物 人 都是肉
Animals, people. They're all meat.
但我知道 这是个不情之请
But I understand this is an unusual request,
我会尽力缓解你的不安
and I want to do everything I can to ease your concerns.
别指望了
Yeah, not happening.
听我说完
Hear me out.
这太蠢了
This is stupid.
你也觉得这蠢吧
You think this is stupid, right?
我觉得路西法
I think when Lucifer,
黑暗王子 地狱之王
Prince of Darkness, King of Hell.
叫你做什么
asks you to do something,
你就照办
you do it.
随便了
Whatever.
随便
Whatever?
你是14岁少女吗
What are you, a 14-year-old girl now?
现在不是
I mean, not right now.
我附身过一个
I possessed one once,
但 并不合适
but … Pbht … it didn't work out.
好多思绪 冲动
A lot of feelings and urges.
哭起来鼻涕眼泪的
and ugly snot crying.
说什么朱莉跟克雷格·卡塞尔在一起了
about how Julie's with Craig Castle now,
虽然他是个帅哥
even though he's total bae,
但她则是个贱婊
but she's, like, a busted bitch on ice.
荷尔蒙 哥们
Hormones, dude.
随便了 赶紧收拾干净
Whatever. Let's clean this up.
然后我们去见他
Then we go meet the man.
我知道 亲爱的 妈妈很快就会回家的
I know, darling. But mommy will be home soon.
我也想你
I miss you, too.
我非常爱你
I love you so, so much.
乖乖的
Be a good boy.
你
You.
萨姆
Now, Sam.
我们开始吧
Let's begin.
图妮·贝维尔 伦敦分会
Toni Bevell, London Chapterhouse.
没错
That's right.
你是什么
So, you're what?
英格兰的记录者吗
You're, uh, English Men of Letters?
不列颠
British.
我们在哪
Where are we?
重要吗
Does it matter?
我只是在想等我杀了你
Just wondering how far I'm gonna have to walk.
要走多远才能回去
back to town after I kill you.
还有她
And her.
不过先杀你
But you first.
好吧 你把我们都杀掉之前
Yes, well, before you murder us all,
我们有几个问题问你 关于你 你哥哥
we do have a few questions about you, your brother,
美国的猎人
Hunters in America,
以及你们是如何拯救太阳的
and how you saved the sun.
好吧 你开枪打我
Right. You shoot me,
绑架我
kidnap me,
但我还是乐意帮忙
but yeah, happy to help.
我并不想伤害你 萨姆
I didn't want to hurt you, Sam.
是你逼我的
You gave me no choice.
而且
And, well,
虽然可以说本不该是这样的
I could say it was never supposed to go this way,
但你是…你
but you're…you.
这本就是不可避免的
It was always going to go this way.
- 你了解我吗 - 我们了解
- And you know me? - We do.
我们观察你和你哥哥多年了
We've been watching you and your brother for years.
自从你们第一次险些毁灭世界
Every since you almost ended the world the first time.
我们还知道路西法 天使坠落
We knew all about Lucifer, the angels falling.
那你们当时在哪
Then where were you?
问得好
Fair question.
我们有些人是想插手的
See, some of us wanted to get involved,
但老头子们不许
but the old men wouldn't allow it.
觉得我们那样就过界了
Thought we were overstepping our bounds.
但经过了黑暗的事
After all this business with the Darkness,
就连他们也承认 事情得有所改变了
even they have to agree, things need to change.
你虽然不信 萨姆
And while you might not believe this, Sam,
但我们是来帮忙的
but we're here to help.
是啊 看得出
Yeah, no, I-I can tell.
我想为把你锁起来道歉
I want to apologize for locking you up.
你有危险 对自己和他人都是
You're dangerous … to others and yourself …
但如果你回答我的问题
but if you answer my questions,
你就能走出去了
you walk right out that door.
我保证
I promise.
- 免了 - 萨姆
- Pass. - Sam.
随你问我什么
You can ask me any kind of question you want.
答应都是一样的
The answer's gonna be the exact same …
去你妈
Screw you.
你想生气吗
You want to get mad?
你想对我动手吗
You want to get mean?
我被魔鬼本人折磨过
I've been tortured by the Devil himself.
你 不过是口音加裤套装
So you, you're just an accent in a pantsuit.
你能把我怎么样
What can you do to me?
冷水澡
A cold shower?
就这招
That's your play?
去你妈
Screw you.
你住这儿
You live here?
嗯 不在外面忙的时候
Yeah, when we're not on the road.
原来是记录者的地堡
It's an old Men of Letters bunker.
- 记录者 - 对
- Men of Letters? - Yeah.
他们是个传说
They're a myth.
是猎人的老故事
An old Hunter's story.
不是的
Not so much.
新行头挺好看
New duds look good.
谢谢
Well, thanks.
总比穿着睡衣到处走好
It's better than walking around in that nightgown the rest …
那是血
That's blood.
是啊
Yeah.
萨姆
Sammy?
小卡
Cass?
拿着
Take this.
留在这儿
Stay here.
迪恩
Dean.
萨姆
Sammy?
手举起来 跪下
Hands in the air. Get on your knees.
你是谁 萨姆在哪
Who are you, and where is Sam?
手举起来
Hands, now.
没事 没事
It's okay. It's okay.
他是友军
He's a friend, all right?
小卡
Hey, Cass.
迪恩
Dean!
好了
Okay. All right.
迪恩
Dean.
- 你活着 - 对
- You're alive? - Yeah.
炸弹和黑暗呢
What about the bomb and the Darkness?
怎么回事
What happened?
我会告诉你一切的 萨姆呢
I'll tell you everything. Where is Sam?
他不在这儿
He's not here.
你是猎人吗
Are you a Hunter?
- 不 我是天使 - 他是天使
- No, I'm an angel. - He's an angel.
再说一遍
Come again?
天使 天打头的
An Angel, with a-a capital "A."
翅膀 竖琴
You know, wings, harp.
我才没有竖琴
No, I don't have a harp.
他是卡西迪奥
This is Castiel.
小卡 这是玛丽
Cass, this is…Mary.
温彻斯特
Winchester.
- 你妈妈 - 对
- Your mother? - ‭Yeah.
等等 萨姆哪去了
So, wait, uh, where … where is Sam?
他不回电话 地板上又有血
He's not answering his phone, there's blood on the floor.
- 怎么回事 - 我不知道
- What's going on? - I don't know.
我们回来时 有个女人等着我们
We came back here, there was a woman waiting for us.
她把我炸飞了
She blasted me away.
我不知道她是谁
I don't know who she was.
我也不知道萨姆去哪了
I don't know what happened to Sam.
我不明白 怎么回事
I don't understand. What happened?
地堡里没人
Okay, well, the bunker's empty,
他们显然是走了
so … so they've obviously left here.
你说女人 不是天使
You said woman … not an angel,
不是恶魔 是个人
not a demon, a-a human.
她是人
She was human.
什么时候的事
When did this go down?
凌晨2：12
2:12 a.m.
那是电脑吗
Is that a-a computer?
是的
Yes.
我不信任那玩意
I don't trust them.
查到了
Got something.
凌晨2：21一辆SUV
An S.U.V. ran a red light.
在离这儿几个街区处闯了红灯
a few blocks from here at 2:21 a.m.
40分钟内没有别的车出现了
And there wasn't another car for 40 minutes.
你怎么做到的
How did you do that?
我黑了交通监控
I hacked the traffic cams.
欢迎来到未来
Welcome to the future.
你觉得是他们吗
You think it's them?
值得一查
It's worth a shot.
妈妈
Mom?
这是约翰的车
This was John's car.
她还那么美
Oh, she's still beautiful.
当然了
Hell, yeah, she is.
亲爱的
Hi, sweetheart.
记得我吗
Remember me?
我们该走了
We should go.
行了吧 萨姆
Can we end this, Sam, please?
去你妈
Screw you.
你以为是怎么回事啊
What do you imagine is happening here?
你以为你这是勇敢
Do you think you're being brave,
你是这里的英雄吗
that you're the hero of this story?
你不是 萨姆
Well, you're no hero, Sam.
你只是不擅长你的工作
You're just bad at your job.
那你就更好吗
Yeah, and you're better?
好多了
So much better.
你走乡间小路 随机处理案子
You drive back roads, catching cases at random.
你听说有人死了 就去看看
You get word a body's dropped, you check it out,
甚至能杀死作恶的东西
and maybe you even kill the thing that did it.
但那人还是死了
But that person is still dead,
可能还要多死几个
and maybe a few more.
但我的人
But my people?
我们提早计划
We plan ahead.
我们研究传说 利用它对付敌人
We study lore, and we use it against our enemies.
在我们那儿 每条大道 每座桥
Back home, every thoroughfare, every bridge,
每个码头 每个机场都有防护符文
every dock, ‭every airport has been warded.
一旦有怪物踏入英国境内
The moment a monster steps foot in Britain,
我们就会知道
we know about it.
20分钟不到 他就会被我们抓到
Within 20 minute', he's been picked up.
40分钟不到 他就会被干掉
And within 40, he's dead.
英国自1965年就没有怪物致死的案例了
There hasn't been a monster-related death in Britain since 1965.
因为我们很擅长我们的工作
because we are good at our job.
你们本就没什么前途 萨姆
Now, you were always a lost cause, Sam,
但我希望有其他我们可以
but I'm hoping there are other Hunters.
与之合作 教导的猎人
we can work with, teach.
我需要你告诉我名字
So, I need you to give me names.
地址 和其他一切
and locations and everything else.
情报传递点 会面地点
Dead drops, meeting places,
组织阶级
an organizational hierarchy,
或许 如果我们齐心合力
because maybe with all of us working together,
就能做到你从来都做不到的
we can do what you never could …
保证美国安全
make America safe.
或许 你会把他们绑在椅子上
Or maybe you tie them to a chair.
或许你还不如我们
Maybe you do worse.
所以 或许
So, maybe…
或许你可以下地狱了
maybe you can go to Hell.
那好吧
Have it your way.
你真要逼我这么做吗
Are you really gonna make me do this?
去 你 妈
Screw…you.
不
No!
别
Don't.
好恶心
So, so gross.
他不是要来跟我们碰面吗
I thought he was supposed to meet us.
干吗
What?
是
Yes.
不 当然 陛下
No, I … Of course, my liege.
我们到了 但是…
We're here, but … but where's…
他说什么呢
What's he saying?
他不肯告诉我他在哪
He won't tell me where he is.
他觉得有人跟踪了我们
He thinks we're being followed.
得了
Come on.
我们不可能被人跟踪了
There's no way we're being followed.
你们好啊
Hello, boys.
路西法
Lucifer?
我得挂了
I, uh, have to go.
还在他身上下赌注呢
Still betting that horse, are we?
是啊 因为我们不蠢
Yeah, 'cause we're not stupid.
继续骗自己吧 亲爱的
Keep telling yourself that, dear.
跟黑暗的一番打斗
That dustup with the Darkness.
肯定对他伤害不轻
must've really taken it out of the old boy.
所以他才一个个地换皮囊
That's why he's jumping from vessel to vessel.
换个不停
to vessel.
所以路西法在逃跑
It's why Lucifer's running …
因为他虚弱不堪
because he's weak.
那又如何
So?
他会强壮起来的
He'll get stronger.
路西法能带我们获得荣耀
Lucifer will lead us to glory.
只要有他在 地狱就不会追随你
As long as he's out there, Hell will never follow you.
就像人说的 「净废话」
Well, like they say, "Duh."
但等我杀了魔鬼
But when I kill the Devil …
你是他的狗
You were his dog.
就算变弱了
Even powered down,
他也还能完爆你个装逼男
he could kick your Posh Spice ass.
现在笑的是谁
Who's laughing now?
一
Eeny…
二
…meeny…
三
…miney…
四
…Mo.
杰米·罗斯
Jamie Ross?
你们是
Who's asking?
昨天你开车载她的金发女
The blond woman that you drove yesterday,
她叫什么
what was her name?
金发女
Blonde?
抱歉 伙计 你搞错了…
Sorry, mate, you got the wrong …
小卡
Cass!
那是天使
That's an angel?
金发女 说名字
Blonde. Name. Now.
我不知道
I-I-I don't know her name.
你知道什么
What do you know?
没人能承受那么多痛还不开口
No one can take that much pain and not break.
没人
No one.
你什么意思
What are you saying?
我…夫人
I th… Ma'am.
如果你想杀他
If you want him dead,
那我马上就割了他的喉咙
then I'll slit his throat right now.
但如果你还想再进一步
But if you want to take this to the next level,
你得打电话了
you need to make the call.
叫来凯奇先生
Bring in Mr. Ketch.
我不要那个疯子接近我
I don't want that psychopath anywhere near me.
那么
So?
So…
我们不再尝试击垮他的身体
we stop trying to break his body.
而是击垮他的头脑
We break his mind.
谢谢
Thank you.
你肯定很难接受吧
This must be difficult for you.
我还记得我最初来到地球的时候
I remember my first moments on Earth.
我吓坏了
It was jarring.
可以这么说吧
One word for it.
我是跟着猎人长大的
I grew up with Hunters.
我听说过人死而复生
I've heard of people coming back from the dead before.
但自己活过来 还隔了30年
But to actually do it… after 30 years.
世界已经改变了好多
A lot's changed.
好多
A lot.
有发现吗
Find anything?
嗯 查了那个谁给我们的机尾号
Yeah, ran the, uh, tail number that what's-his-face gave us.
邪恶女王到达时乘的飞机
The plane that Evil Elsa flew in on.
登记为外交飞机
has diplomatic registry.
所以呢
Which means?
所以其飞行计划是机密
Which means its flight plans are sealed.
除非你想黑进国务院去
unless you want to hack the State Department.
他们是谁
Who are these people?
（格雷戈里·马里恩医生 兽医）
迪恩
Dean.
（格雷戈里·马里恩医生 兽医诊所）
马里恩医生 让我们进去吧
Dr. Marion, how about you let us in?
你就什么都没问 把子弹从他腿里挖出来了
So, you dug the bullet out of his leg, no questions asked?
她给了我10万块
She offered me 100 grand.
你拿了
And you took it?
学生贷款是很重的负担
Student loans were a bitch, okay?
小卡 小卡 别伤害他
Cass! Cass! Cass! Don't hurt him.
还不到时候
Not yet.
听着
All right, look,
她没说名字
she didn't give me her name.
我们完事后 司机走了
When we were done, the driver bailed,
我拿了钱
I got paid,
有另一个小妞过来了
and then some other chick shows up,
他们一起开走了
and they all drive away.
你就知道这些了
And that's everything you know?
嗯
Yeah.
是啊
Totally.
伤害他吧
Hurt him.
我有她的电话号码
I have her phone number!
好吧 听着
Okay? Okay, look, look, look.Look,
我不知道他们在哪
I don't know where they are,
但她几小时前打给了我
but she called me a couple hours ago …
几小时前
a few hours ago,
问我给他打的镇定剂的事
asking about the sedative I gave the guy.
所以我有她的电话号码
So…I've got her phone number.
我觉得这不行
I don't think it's working.
等等
Wait.
很快 他就会求着回答我们了
Soon, he'll be begging to answer our questions.
只要能让那停下
Anything to make it stop.
马里恩医生
Dr. Marion.
我是打来
Yeah, I'm just calling, you know,
问问病人情况的
to, uh, check on the patient.
出什么事了吗 医生
Is everything all right, doctor?
没事 非常好
Yeah, yeah, sure. Definitely.
我要挂了
I'm hanging up now.
听着 贱人
Listen, bitch.
我不管你是谁 我不管你想要什么
I don't care who you are, I don't care what you want.
你抓了我弟弟
You have my brother.
迪恩·温彻斯特
Dean Winchester.
我听说你死了
I heard you were dead.
你听错了
Well, you heard wrong.
我给你个机会 就一个
Now, I'm gonna give you one chance … just one …
把萨姆还回来
to hand Sam back.
抱歉 不行
Sorry. Not possible.
你以为你逃得过我吗
Oh, you think you can run from me?
试试吧
Try it.
等我找到你
Because when I find you …
我会找到你的
and I will find you …
如果他不是完好无损 我就把你拆了
if he is not in one piece, I will take you apart.
听懂了吗
You understand me?
我们有麻烦了
We have a problem.
放我出去
Let me out!
现在呢
Now what?
我们有她的号码
Well, we got her number.
我们回地堡 进行追踪
Let's head back to the bunker, and we'll put a trace on it.
妈妈
Mom?
她失去意识了 但没有严重损伤
She's unconscious, but there's no serious damage.
好吧 那帮帮她
All right. Help her.
迪恩·温彻斯特吧
Dean Winchester, I presume.
杰西卡
Jessica.
你该更小心点的
You should be more careful.
你手机上有定位服务
with your location services on your phone.
你是他们的一员吗
Are you one of them?
我是他们的一员
I'm one of them.
嗯
Yeah.
告诉我我弟弟在哪
You tell me where my brother is,
我或许就不对你下狠手
and I might take it easy on you.
别手软了
Oh, please don't.
找这个吗
Looking for this?
那第二轮
So, round two?
有人来吗
Anyone?
死了 我是因为你才死了
Dead. I'm dead because of you.
我是因为你才死了
I'm dead because of you.
这都怪你
This is all your fault.
- 都怪你 - 迪恩
- This is your fault. - Dean?
我们都是因为你才死了 萨姆
We're all dead because of you, Sam.
本该是你的 本该是你的
It should've been you. It should've been you.
你是个怪物 你是个怪物
You're a freak. You are a freak.
你是个怪物
You're a freak.
都怪你
It's your fault.
你说得对
You're right.
我以为
You know, I would've thought.
你们俩这样的壮小伙儿
for two strapping lads like yourselves,
战斗力能再强点呢
you would've lasted a tad longer.
但是 常言说得好
But hey, you know what they say.
好事都…
Good things come to those …
谢谢 妈妈
Thanks, Mom.
都怪你
Your fault!
都怪你 死吧
It's your fault. Just die.
都怪你 都怪你
It's your fault. It's your fault.
It's your fault. It's all your fault.
死吧
Just die.
你为什么不死 萨姆
Why won't you die, Sam?
你为什么不死
Why don't you die?
都怪你
It's your fault.
不
No.
或许你并不那么擅长你的工作
Maybe you're not as good at your job as you think.
不
No! No!
No!
不
在她车上找到了手机
Found her cellphone in the car.
最后一通电话是从密苏里州奥尔德里奇打来的
Last phone call was made from Aldrich, Missouri.
萨姆应该在那一带
We're guessing Sam's probably around there.
好
Good.
太好了
That's great.
你没事吧
You okay?
有事
No.
对不起 我…
I'm sorry. I just…
我这辈子都在逃避这个 猎魔
I spent my life running from this, from hunting.
我脱离了
And I got out.
我从来不希望你和萨姆过这样的生活
I never wanted this for you and Sam.
妈妈 我懂的
Mom, I-I get it.
我真懂
I do.
如果我有孩子 也不会希望他们做这个
If I had kids, I wouldn't want them in this.
但萨姆和我
But Sam and me…
救人猎魔
saving people and hunting things,
这是我们的生活
this is our life.
我觉得我们让世界更美好了
I think we make the world a better place.
我确定
I know that we do.
目击者称他大汗淋漓 脸色苍白 疯疯癫癫
Witnesses say he was sweating and pale and psycho.
自称他是路西法
He said his name was freaking Lucifer.